tagline for my company [music] is
humanizing AI for care. We've talked
about how healthcare needs to be
emotionally ready before it can be
technologically ready. [music]
Help people feel safe, seen, and
empowered as that change happens.
latchment on something which is already
there and bend on that
>> and hundreds of thousands of dollars on
the data that powers the technology.
>> Why is verification
not model accuracy the hardest problem
that you actually have to solve?
>> But AI what gives us ability to kind of
search through the much wider grid of
possible compounds and molecules and
biomolelecules. The whole idea of AI now
is to be able to fail in faster so we
can get faster to and actually correct
result. And
>> today's guest is David Finkelshteyn, CEO
of Pivotal AI, where he focuses on
building AI systems for pharmaceutical
life sciences use cases that can
actually be verified, defended, and
trusted. We're going to go beyond the
hype today to talk about the real
bottleneck in pharma AI verification.
Not making models faster, but making
their outputs defensible enough to
survive regulators, audits, and real
world consequences. David, welcome to
the signal room. We're looking forward
to having this conversation with you for
a while now. We're we're in some pretty
interesting times, and I know you're
doing a lot of great work in in in the
pharmaceutical industry right now, among
other things that you're working on. But
if you don't mind, I'd love to just kind
of jump right in with some some
questions. cuz I know I've got a lot to
learn and I'm sure my listeners are
going to be very interested in what you
have to say today. So let's talk about
pharma AI. When people talk about it,
they focus on discovery speed more often
than almost anything else. Why is
verification
not model accuracy the hardest problem
that you actually have to solve?
>> Um yeah, thank you first of all. Thank
you for having me here. Yeah, I'm I'm
excited to excited to be here and to
share some uh of my uh experience. It's
always pleasure to have an conversation
with uh smart people. So,
>> let me go get one for you.
>> Oh, come on. So, answering your
question, I don't think is one of the
more is more important than another. I
think they tied together and the
discovery itself just doesn't make sense
without verification because we should
be able to get something a molecule the
drug that will fit some requirement
parameters. So it should be pleasurable
in terms of like phocinetics phramics uh
it should uh fulfill admin parameters.
Um so in this sense how like yes we
discovered something but what is it we
discovered right and this this this our
discovery should be tightened together
with verification
uh uh in our computer and then we want
to get down to
5 10 50 100 molecules and we want to
actually synthesize them in the lab and
we want to test them
>> and like it this this can be we can
start we should start with uh purely
invittor test because it's the cheapest
one and we this way we will cut off a
lot of uncertainty because again our
model regardless how good is it and how
accurate is it how model itself how
verified is it we need a ground truth
and ground truth is like actual physical
molecules being synthesized
>> right
>> regardless of small molecules and big
molecules so here it's just generating
molecule without verification just
doesn't make sense,
>> right? I understand that. You know, you
you rais an an excellent point as well
in terms of the realities of what what
we're using now with AI. It's just it
hasn't been you available to us for very
long. It it does require a lot of due
diligence especially in this space that
you're working in. I I I really
appreciate your perspective on that. I
think it's for me it's comforting. I
hope it is for others as well. Let's
think about the outputs. Uh so when
you're when you're using AI where are
the where are the most common ways or
the that between discovery and
regulatory acceptance where do things
really break down?
>> So there are many possible points on
breaking down and again it doesn't come
specifically for you. So most of the
break points they are the same
regardless of the way we discover the
leads. So there is a possible break
points when we trying to synthesize it.
Then when we trying to test parameters
and and um of of the drug in vitro then
when we go from invitro to invivo like
in the living creatures unfortunately we
still need to do this. Then when we
selecting a like clinical target group
then when we go into the human testing.
So all these points are possible break
point there are um specific for
artificial intelligence like for for
this way of generation drugs there are
specific break points for this way and
they are again it's it's just a other
side of the metal because on on one hand
what AI what gives us ability to kind of
search through the much wider grid of
possible compounds and molecules and
biomolelecules. So because before let's
say we can like we knew some number of
molecules and like as a humanity we were
inventing them and we were making like
steps and now they seem very like little
steps compared to what we can do now
with all this computational power and uh
machine learning power
>> but so like we did already a lot of
tests on all these compounds and
molecules all sorts of like testing
again in vitro in vivo all sort types of
research
of these molecules and but so when we AI
gives us ability to simulate experiments
with something far far away from what we
already have something looks completely
sim completely like different unlike
regard if it's with a small molecule
again or or a protein we can using AI we
can design like using AlphaFold let's
say we can design a protein that we've
never met in a human body or in an
animal body just something artificial
and and AlphaFold will predict how it
will fold in space and this is great
however the verification when
verification came into place it's this
unseen protein may cause I'm again like
may cause our body not to accept it may
cause an allergic reaction and because
it's not it doesn't look like anything
we've seen before we have no information
almost no information and guess about
it. So we just have to make more tests
and again this is a possible point of
breakdown
>> right
>> yeah and this is I would say yeah
>> the speed that you mentioned I I think
this is the piece that gets me excited
but I can see all when you're talking
about validation it also complicates
matters but but you're able to really
look at a much broader set of of
information and simulate and model
different things that would take you a
very very long time before having that
cap capability, but then you got to play
catch-up on the validation side. That
that must be it's exciting to to know
how far fast you can go, but there's
some work that you just can't shortcut.
I imagine that's a bit of a a
frustrating point as you're as you're
learning and and developing new new
compounds.
>> I mean, yeah, it depends on the
perspective. It's it's it can be
frustrated on one hand and another hand
knowing that we are like safer from I
mean I'm as a person who have been
working with machine learning models
more than 10 years I can tell you that
sometimes they so much off like they
completely off so it's it's actually
makes me feel safer knowing that our
validation criteria hasn't been changed
for a specifically that being said
>> at least you know that you you can fail
faster and that's one of the benefits
Right.
>> Exactly. And this is very very important
because again 90 like I don't remember
exactly um I think around 90% or even
more of all drugs that after they were
selected as a drug candidates. So this
whole industry right everyone knows that
create a new molecule denovo molecu even
generic but specific know is like huge
money tons amount of money. You can't
just you know be a startup or just
enthusiast and just create new molecule.
you have you have to get tremendous
amount of money and big part of it is
this huge failing rate and the whole
idea and you you catch it up like it's
this the whole idea of AI now is to be
able to failing faster so we can get
faster to an actually correct result
instead of like putting a lot of hours
and and efforts and human hours into and
work into something that will fail in
months now we will know it will pass
even our machine learning threshold in a
week.
>> That's a massive impact. That's exciting
cuz I think think about the broader uses
of AI for clinical research as well. I
think this is a really exciting time
that we're entering into. We thought the
co vaccines came out quickly. That's
probably just scratching the surface of
what's going to be possible as we learn
how to use this the AI capabilities uh
more efficiently moving forward. I've
heard the the term blackbox way too
often when they're talking about data AI
in in in any industry. Why do those
models fail specifically in
pharmaceutical environments?
>> Uh what so what do you mean by failing
>> So you know the idea of trusting
>> AI not necessarily having enough
visibility into exactly how it's
deriving the outputs that you see. So
where is that really problematic in the
work that you do? Yeah. So this is the
essence of machine learning modeling per
se. So we have have a kind of this
trade-off. It's not like we there are
workarounds. We can talk about more
later. But the the rule of s there is a
trade-off. The more complex model the
the more complex the task usually the
more complex model you need and the more
complex the model
the less transparent it is. Because for
us transparency is something that we can
understand, we can relate. can grasp
right because like the easiest the most
simple machine learning model what is it
it's just a a line right it's I think
every data science first lesson you have
a graph and you have some dots going
approximately this direction and
everyone being asked okay guys now tell
me predict where next dots going to be
in this graph and now everyone drawing
this line and saying okay it's going
this direction say congratulations you
just uh make made your first prediction
as a like as machine learning model
would do. So it's we understand where
this machine learning would come from
right it's very simple
>> but when and then like there is a lure
of complexity and at the end we have a
large language models it's a narrow
network with very complex structure with
hundreds of billions of weights and of
course when you look at it like and you
have input and output there is no way a
human can tell okay this I think I know
what this will give me right in the end
so it's able it is able to solve very
complex task because it the structure is
so complex and flexible and this makes
it not uh explainable so much. So we
can't understand
>> people can't not [clears throat] always
can understand the reasoning behind um
this like decisions that machine models.
That's such an important thing, too, is
we we really need to make sure that
we're we're thinking about how we're
working with AI. We we have to have
explanability and transparency,
particularly when it comes to anything
that's going to touch clinical care or
is going to be some sort of a treatment
that that a human being is going to be
subjected to. regulations are a little
bit slow and coming when it comes to to
this side of everything, but I don't
think we have a whole lot of time left
before that starts to ramp. It sounds
I'm starting to hear a lot more about it
now. Hopefully, we can be proactive
enough in the industry that we don't
have things done to us, which is usually
how regulation affects us. We got people
who are really not understanding the
tech the technologies. They don't
understand medicine. they're trying to
make policy and that's that's just it's
a recipe for disaster in my opinion
particularly in the space that we're
talking about just because um if you're
dealing with it from a regulatory
standpoint you're thinking about it from
the legal and risks lens and the people
that are having those conversations are
certainly not trained scientists they're
not trained clinicians for the most part
now there are a few but very few of them
are actually in regulatory roles I
really appreciate that the context that
that you're giving it what does it mean
to actually verify an AI insight in in
the in the context of drug development.
>> So the the closest thing to verify an
AI. So when we define defining the model
again it we getting back to what we
discussed at the beginning right the
model the model output there are just
some numbers the context is what is it
important for the model. So we should
define clear several things. First we
should define the um the specific use
cases the frame within which we can
apply this model right because again uh
there are models that can predict uh
train models that generally speaking can
predict pretty good let's call again
everyone knows I think alpha fall right
alpha fall can predict pretty good how
molecules are folding in space and
they're really doing a good job there we
want and I will give you an extreme
example just on that we want regardless
of how put AlphaFold in predicting
molecules looks in space. We won't rely
on AlphaFold to predict a new drug
against some kind of cancer just because
it's not intended to do this. It it
wasn't trained to do this. It wasn't
validated to do this. It's it's not the
job of this model. So first thing is a
specific use case. The second thing is a
data created data. It's very very
important that how we what kind of data
we use to train and test the model. Um
right
>> again I I I don't think it should be a
guide for data scientists how exactly to
do this but high level data should be
should fit some statistical distribution
which it shouldn't have too much
outliers too many outliers
>> um or at least they should be again
distributed well when we test when we
validate in the model we should avoid
this thing called data leakage
>> right
>> so it means we should really separate
the data which we're using to train the
model and that we're using to to
validate the model and often as a data
scientists we have an urge when when we
have a new data and sometimes it's very
like exciting new data some new can
gives us new insights we have an urge to
retrain our model using this new data so
this is very dangerous part because if
we retrain this model using this new
data we should have another test set to
validate this model again because
otherwise
>> we may overfeit our model. Meaning it
will show very good results in our train
data obviously in in our validation set
which is not purely validation anymore
and therefore we cannot say how well it
will fit the pattern not the specific
noise in in in our data set. So this is
this is very important. Yeah, I'd say
these are main things.
>> You mentioned context and I want to kind
of stay on that topic for for a minute
here because I think that's one of the
things that I'm starting to find out
that people really are not as diligent
as they should be in in how they're
using AI. And I think the risk that is
now emerging because we we've got two
companies that are now entering the
health care space from a consumer access
standpoint and I mean I wonder if maybe
you can talk a little bit about how
important context is even in a larger
sense because we're talking about people
just interacting with chat GPT health or
with cloud health. These are AI
companies the data that they're working
with it's because it's sitting in
platforms that are considered to be
administrative and not clinical. It
changes the dynamics in terms of who's
responsible for decision-m and if it's
not involving a clinician and it's
sitting on a platform like that in most
most situations we're not talking about
liability even being a possibility. So
missing context I think is going to be
something that we have to really pay
attention to. Talk a little bit about
that from your perspective and why it's
such an important part of what you're
doing. So yes um the first thing I want
to say here I in my opinion it's really
important that people
um uh trying to know more and figure out
more about their own life especially
about their own health. So when you when
you have a appointment to doctor or when
it's when it's heard and you like you do
your own research before going and
blindly trust someone even if this is a
trained specialist unfortunately we know
that not everyone
even in in this area um the same right
there are true specialists and and not
so good. So it's always good to have
your own opinion and your and enable
your critical thinking uh supported by
some knowledge. That being said, of
course everyone
I'm sure especially everyone who is
listening your podcast knows that Chip,
Jimnina, I don't know Claude, all of
them they they hallucinate and they do
this on a daily basis pretty often,
right? Yes. So again my rule of thumb
here is always always try to find the
ground truth the origin reference. So
and again like they not hallucinating
because they are stupid or because they
don't know actually no because they
don't know. They they hallucinating
because they don't know but if you give
them enough context it's a very powerful
analytics tool. So they can extract
knowledge from again they can gather and
extract knowledge from different sources
different type of references. So what I
suggest the golden bus I think is to
whenever you want to the first thing
whenever you want to do research do your
research but when you're using any LLM
request it to work with a real source
and of course again the the golden
standard scientific article. So if you
want to research something about any
type of symptoms or or disease just ask
it to give you a bunch of references and
give you a suggestions based of it.
[snorts] And the second of course all
right after this go to the doctor have
your knowledge gather your knowledge and
go to the doctor. You're not trained
enough neither me nor you. No one
trained trained enough unless you're a
specialist. So do your research and go
to the doctor.
That is perfectly sad and I think people
really need to hear that message. We we
probably should put that on repeat and
turn the volume up honestly because the
the context issue was from my standpoint
just because of my own experiences. I
can't remember things that happened 25
years ago that actually might be
entirely relevant for the condition that
I'm that I'm dealing with right now. And
if I can't remember it, the model's
certainly not going to have that
information available. So that the
context has got to be something that
people think about and it's only like
you said it's not hallucinating because
of anything except for really the lack
of access to information. There's a lot
of things that go into that and I think
the things that I get concerned about
are symptoms that for all by themselves
they might be low risk and there'd be no
red flags set off but with proper
context if it happens to
be relevant that 2 years ago I I had a
really difficult time healing my broken
leg cuz I I had a wound. that kind of
information in current context might
mean something completely different than
just the symptoms that you're trying to
figure out what what to do about now.
That's just in my own thinking. I mean,
I know that they're they're working
through deploying the doctor's version
and the you know a a patient's version,
but again still the context is
important. I am on medication for my
blood pressure. The model may not know
that. the model might just say I've got
high blood pressure and it alerts and I
actually go to the physician and I'm
taking up time uh that I don't need to
be taking which means the physician may
not be treating someone that really
needs treatment because I'm in there and
I don't need to be. So I mean there's
like a lot of different sides to this
but in the context
>> it's really really critical. Let let me
uh add my five cents here. Actually very
interesting
trend I am seeing now in the industry is
again because uh everyone who has
internet and uh $20 in the pocket uh
have access to like great analytics
slashn knowledge base analytical
knowledge base. It's a good it's it's a
big trend for patients to own own their
own data
>> right
>> meaning when you go to the doctor right
you went there they gave you they made
it their may rust some tests and then
they say you some tell you something and
give one paper where it says like what
they did and and and what the doctor did
and you a very organized person if one
year later you have this paper somewhere
it's rare case actually but but the
clinician the clinic the the uh the
hospital they always have your data.
They gather it, they store it because
they have to. And for you to own this
data to be able to again use the whole
context for maybe LLM tool or another
specialist to look at it. This is a a
big trend I'm seeing now in in the
software development in this area and
and in healthcare in general. Yeah, this
it's going to be an interesting year
because we started right out of the gate
and we're not even halfway through well,
I guess maybe we are about just halfway
through today, halfway through January.
Um, yeah, it's it's going to be
interesting to see where where things go
from here. I want to kind of get into
some things around data integrity and
data quality because that's that's one
of the other issues that we're we're
dealing with. And you know, you talk
about the absence of data. From my
standpoint, that's the scariest kind of
bias that we could be dealing with. Talk
a little bit about, you know, how you
how do you manage when you're trying to
determine where to focus? How difficult
is it to validate whether you actually
have all the right inputs, the right
data sources, and you you've got
sufficient data integrity and quality
that you can actually trust it and start
to move forward.
>> Yeah, it's a great question. I saying
this is uh it's actually the biggest
bottleneck in in AI in drug design
development in healthcare and AI and in
general in all data science tasks. So
it's um really now the data is is like a
gold everyone is running around trying
to get more data, generate more data and
this is another problem synthetic data
but again it's a it's a like big topic.
Yes, you you need to
very carefully
get select get and select sources of
your information. Curate the data. Uh
make sure that it the the origin the
sources of this data are trustworthy
and then you need to maintain integrity
indeed. And uh it sounds easy but
actually it's not
>> because
because there are a lot of errors happen
along the way from from where you find
the data to when it comes into the model
to train it
>> and [snorts] all the things usually
related with humans. So human error the
good thing that the again in theory the
path to the integrity is pretty
straightforward. You need you just need
your system fully traceable, audible and
you you have to log everything. Again,
it sounds easy. It's not in reality, but
this is like this is how you do. This is
how you ensure integrity of your data.
Make sure in every step along the way of
your data pipeline, you can always look
backwards and and every step you you you
know what happened with your data, how
it was transformed, what what happened,
how it was like brushed and selected and
created. So this this is the way to
again preserve the integrity,
>> right? Yeah. It's such an important
factor and I I think that just thinking
about context again like when when it
comes to you know clinical care facts
change and when you're you've trained
your models to look at things a certain
way you've got all kinds of historical
data there it may be actually just fine
but the reality is things do change and
if the model is not aware of what's
changed then it's going to give you
outputs that are going to take you in a
direction you don't want to go I think
the real important thing for us to
remember is when you're talking about
healthcare It's called the practice of
medicine for a very specific reason.
It's an evolving science. It's not
static. And unfortunately, a lot of the
regulatory agencies are they treat it
like it is static. And that's how things
are measured. Whatever the composite is
that you're measured against to
determine whether your quality is good
or not. You're either incentivized or
penalized. It's based on a composite
that no human being will ever look like.
And it's just a really important thing,
especially when we're talking about
using uh LLM as a consumer. Remember,
you are unique. The model doesn't know
who you are and it doesn't care and it's
certainly not going to have any
compassion for you. So, you know, you
got to just be aware of what it really
is. And the incomplete risk, you know,
from in terms of having not enough data
or not the right data, it's the same
issue that a clinician has now when they
look at us in the exam room. They're
wondering what don't they know and is it
important? AI is not going to solve that
problem. It may help to accelerate the
processing of information and eliminate
a few more risks or even diagnostics,
but it's still not going to be able to
give you the the precision that everyone
wants. Yeah. I think that what I would
also say to what you mentioned earlier
in terms of how people should be
thinking about it, you also need to
remember when when you're putting your
PHI into a tool like that, you're also
eliminating your own protections by
doing so. people really need to be very
very careful how they think about using
these things and just remember to your
point do your research but go see your
doctor. It's just it's really important
to do that.
>> So for sure
>> let let's talk about what I kind of
touched on there and it's maybe the
uncomfortable part of what we're dealing
with.
>> What are the weaknesses that are most
often surfacing during audits or
regulatory reviews or legal scrutiny?
because I mean obviously you guys have
to think a lot about that when you're
dealing with research and
experimentation to actually get to some
of the exciting breakthroughs that you
get to. So again uh I talking about
breakthrough spec um uh like problems
specifically for drugs designed with
help of AI uh or
>> in general for
>> I think it's across the board because I
mean in both in both perspectives you
know it's still it's still an issue
that's got to be you know thought about
and weighed as just the the pace and I
don't want to overuse the term blackbox
but to regulators you know a lot of this
stuff is going to seem like a black box
cuz they already have a language barrier
and that they don't understand the
scientific language that's used half the
time or probably more than half the
time.
>> Yeah. Again, for regulator like okay
there are two kind of if I talk about if
you're talking about AI in let's say
drug development and drug design there
are two we can divide our AI tools or
approaches by two types. First type is
when we and this is where we where we
working mostly uh as pivotal and we were
talking during this podcast mostly
generating new leads so new new
candidates for drugs right so this and
for usually for the regulators for the
authorities for FDA EMA they don't care
much how we came up with this drug with
this uh new molecule because anyway we
going to undergo all the same tests that
other denovo molecules going through
regardless of the way we came up with
this molecules. Right? So again it's um
maybe someday down the road we will be
able to like convincing be more
convincing with the reasoning how we
came up with this. But again at this
point it doesn't really matter how do
you how did you came up with this
molecule that you want to test. It's
just going through the standard bus. Now
another type of machine learning tools
or AI tools uh that comes into the
pharmaceutical area these are more
decision makers and they not really in
the designing your drugs
>> right
>> uh they more in the analyzing
information for example
uh the biggest uh example of it it's uh
proved by EMA let me look it up I don't
uh remember the name exactly uh
of this
uh this company this tool. Give me one
second. I will look them up.
>> Yeah. So, aim uh uh NASH this is uh
essentially as a uh AI assistant for
histologology scoring in mesh trails. So
it's a AMI approved tool that help makes
a decision and this is a completely
different thing right. So this is
essentially became a part of validation
chain and again we don't have because
people don't trust AI and for good it's
good they don't trust EA uh
>> right
>> this we don't have a lot of so I think I
uh this is the only one of its own kind
that essentially allowed into the uh as
a decision maker without human overview
too much. So we just just not there yet.
>> Right. As we're kind of getting to
towards the end here, want to maybe take
a take a look out in into the future a
little bit. Uh first, we have talked
about hallucinations, but what would you
tell people that they should be thinking
about in in terms of how can you prevent
them in in the in in the work that
you're in the pharmaceutical industry in
particular? Because I'm sure there's a
lot of folks out there that are
wrestling with how to use it, how not to
use it. you know the hallucination piece
of it I think is is something be very
interesting to understand where you
think that needs to go.
>> Um so again it really depends on what
you want to do with this. Uh in general
again the rule of thumb if you want LM
to hallucinate less give it more
context. The more context the more data
you will fit uh LM the less it will go
hallucinated. essentially think about it
think uh about LM as a very powerful uh
search analytics tool. So just don't ask
it to invent something. Ask it to
analyze and work with the data and
context you gave it.
>> Beautifully said. I don't know that that
can be overstated. That that's amazing.
As you're looking ahead, do you think uh
verification is going to be really
become a real competitive advantage
rather than a constraint? Yes, I seen
now and it's not like again it's in a
different stage of drug design. The
chain is very long from idea to actual
drug in the pharmacy. The the the chain
is tremendous. So and many steps in this
chain they involves a lot of
documentation about a a lot of paper pap
papers filled and this is where I take
over now taking over now because as we
all know works with documentations
filling papers like based on your input
fill some standardized templates papers
from authorities this is m is driving it
right it it doing it great and there are
all sorts of kind of tools emerging now
to taking over this task. And this is
great because again this is something
that we shouldn't like there weren't any
harm from this because they cannot spoof
any evidence or push something some
drugs that will be toxic or harmful in
any way. Just there is a bureaucracy
threshold and now we have a tool to
fight with this bureaucracy at least at
some portion of it. So this is where we
see our acceleration.
I think again it's uh seeing how fast we
evolving in this industry and how like
pivots every year in in this industry
and other industry. But yeah it's
prediction is very hard thing to do. I'm
not a good machine learning models to
get a good prediction. what what I can
say I think that again first uh we will
uh
try to do something with lowhanging
fruits which are working with the
commmentations and maybe AI will let us
to reduce amount of efforts we have to
put into the bureaucracy and the the red
tape and this will lead us and like data
scientists and biochemists and like
other scientists and smart people in
pharma to put their mind more into the
essence of it into the creating or
creation of new drugs. Um getting back
to our very first topic, we may be able
to shorten this loop of designing and
verification and now we there are loops
where we designing drugs in AI and then
we send candidates to the automate
robotic lab and this labs they generates
molecules and they send them so not
generate a test the molecules send the
result back. So it's kind of closing
this loop and we need less and less
human in it and this is very good. So
the very good high quality verification
loop will lead us to a faster drug
invention and uh probably higher quality
medicine.
>> Exciting. There's there's just so many
things that weren't possible a decade
ago that now are going to become
reality. I think there's more
groundbreaking discoveries coming in the
cancer space. It wasn't that long ago
that a cancer diagnosis really came with
a an unfortunate time frame that you're
dealing with because it's it wasn't
curable. Um, but the things are evolving
so quickly in the work that you you're
doing in the pharmaceutical space.
Incredibly important. David, as we're
wrapping up, if folks wanted to uh reach
out to you to have a conversation
because I'm I'm sure that you you've
shared some things that'll folks will
have some curiosity about and want to
get some some insight from you. How how
do they reach out to you? What's your
preference?
>> So yeah, you can reach out mainly my
LinkedIn profile. I hope link will be
under the in the description, right?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. And or uh there is a form on our
website where you can uh ask a question
or submit a request for project or
consultation. Uh
>> perfect. Yeah. For for listeners, I I'll
make sure that his contact information
and the website is in the show notes. So
David, thank you so much for a really
practical and grounded conversation. I
think you hit some themes in a on a high
level that folks really need to be
cognizant of. Context, context, context.
Big big focus on that. I really really
appreciate it. And I'm sure that uh the
clinical folks that are listening out
there appreciate that message too.
Context is important, but when you've
done your research, go see your doctor.
>> That's it for this episode of the Signar
Room. If today's conversation sparked
something in you, an idea, a challenge,
or a perspective worth amplifying, I'd
love to hear from you. Message me on
LinkedIn or visit cigarroompodcast.com
to explore being a guest on an upcoming
episode. Until next time, stay tuned,
stay curious, and stay human.